{
    "id": "4b457caab923433f838e150a0ef5b827",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Grandpa …………………………. for a walk every morning.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about habitual actions.",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "is going",
                "will go"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "All mothers ………………………… their children.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about general truths.",
            "answers": [
                "love",
                "will love",
                "would love"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The British once ………………………… India.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about finished events.",
            "answers": [
                "was ruling",
                "ruled",
                "rules"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Grandpa ………………………… to the temple yesterday.",
            "description": "We used the simple past to say that something happened sometime ago.",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… something last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "was hearing",
                "hears"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. gently to the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "spoke",
                "speak"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The pond …………………………… up every summer.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about routines, habitual actions etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "dry",
                "dries",
                "dried"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Humble words …………………………… others joy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "gives",
                "gave"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………….. a living by mending shoes.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about people’s professions.",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "makes",
                "is making"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… school at fourteen.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to say that something happened in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "was leaving",
                "has left",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The puppy ………………………….. by a group of boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rescued",
                "was rescued",
                "has rescued"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}